- Hey, can I ask you a question?  - Sure.
- 嘿 我能问你个问题吗?  - 当然
You've had this dart board since I've known you,
从我认识你开始 这靶子就在了
but I've never seen you play.
但我从来没见你玩过飞镖
Oh, uh, we played... once.
哦 我们玩过... 一次
I broke a window.
我把窗户砸破了
What window?
什么窗户?
That one over there.
就是那边那扇
Leonard, where are the Skee-Ball tickets?
Leonard 投球奖券在哪儿?
Skee-Ball tickets?
什么投球奖券?
Yeah, from when we went to the arcade three years ago?
就是我们三年前去游戏机房玩的时候赢来的
I finally decided what prize I want.
我终于决定要换什么奖品了
Hurry up.
快点
Uh, if I still have them,
如果我还留着
they're probably in the junk box.
估计就在废料箱里
Ooh, what are you gonna get?
你想换什么?
None of your business.
不关你的事
But when you see me wearing a flower
但如果你一会儿看到我
in my lapel later,
在翻领上带了朵花儿
you are most welcome to sniff it.
很欢迎你来嗅嗅香味
Yup, oh... here you go.
好了... 给你
Oh, thank you.
谢谢
Here, get yourself an eraser for your troubles.
给你 去换个橡皮擦玩吧
Oh.
哦
Oh-ho.
这个
I forgot about this.
我都忘了这个了
My aunt made it for me when I started college.
我考上大学的时候 我婶婶给我做的
Aw, did she hate you?
她是不是讨厌你?
Why? Because I got an ugly, itchy sweater,
为什么这么说? 就因为给了我一件扎人的丑毛衣
and my brother got a car? No, I was her favorite.
而给了我弟弟一辆车吗? 当然不 我是她最爱的孩子
Yeah, I seem to be a few tickets short.
好吧 好像还缺几张奖券
Are there more in the box?
盒子里还有吗?
Hmm, I think I got them all.
我好像都拿出来了
Nope, they're not in there.
没了 里面没了
Well, you barely looked. Let me see.
你都没好好找 我来看看
No, no, no, I... I looked, and...
才不是 我... 我找了...
no more tickets.
没有奖券了
Leonard, let me look in the box.
Leonard 让我看看盒子里有什么
Okay, okay!
好吧 好吧!
I'm gonna show you what's in the box.
我会给你看盒子里的东西
But just... promise not to flip out.
但你得保证... 别发疯
Why would I flip out?
我干嘛要发疯?
Is it a spider?
里面有蜘蛛吗?
It's a spider!
真的有蜘蛛!
No, if it was a spider,
不 如果真的有蜘蛛
Lenny would've flipped out.
Lenny肯定先疯了
Okay, Sheldon,
好吧 Sheldon
I know I was supposed to return
我知道我很早之前
this DVD a long time ago,
就该去把这张碟还掉
and I know we rented it
我也知道是用你的卡
on your card.
租的
But it's been, like, seven years
但都已经过去快七年了
and clearly nothing bad has happened.
也没发生什么坏事
So in... in... in... instead of being
所以... 与其和平时一样
a giant pain in the ass like you always are,
你又叫又闹 使劲折腾
what if
能不能
this one time you just tried staying calm?
这次就试着冷静点呢?
That seems like a reasonable request.
这要求好像挺合理的
Although so did, "Hey, Leonard, would you mind
但我还是得说 "嘿 Leonard 你能不能
returning that DVD?"
把碟去还了?"
I'm sorry. I'll... I'll take care of it.
对不起 我... 我会去还掉的
Okay.
好吧
I mean it, I'm going to.
我是说真的 真的会去还
I believe you.
我相信你
And you're going to stay calm?
而你会继续保持冷静?
I said I would.
我说过会的
How about that?
怎么样?
Sheldon's being reasonable.
Sheldon讲道理了
Yeah, it's freaking me out.
没错 我被吓到了
I'm gonna go.
我还是走吧
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* That all started with a big bang *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
生活大爆炸 第七季第八集
生活大爆炸 第七季第八集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==-- 仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==-- 仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见 时间轴：pisces夜 翻译：失眠影 学渣酥 Wholessness 初见 校对：uu要A
协调：初见 时间轴：pisces夜 翻译：失眠影 学渣酥 Wholessness 初见 校对：uu要A
So... when you say
所以... 你说
you're not going to freak out about the DVD,
你不会为了影碟的事乱发疯
here's what that means.
应该包括以下几点
Don't fixate on it.
别盯着这件事
Don't wake me up in the middle of the night.
别大半夜把我叫醒
Or nag me through the door
别在我上厕所的时候
while I'm on the toilet.
隔着门教训我
Okay, first, talking to you while you're on the toilet
首先我得说清楚 你上厕所的时候和你说话
isn't exactly a picnic for me either, okay?
我也不好受 好吗?
Remember...
记得...
when you can hear me, I can hear you.
你能听到我讲话 我也能听到你放屁
And second...
其次...
you completely disregard
你完全忽略了
how uncomfortable unresolved issues are for me.
未尽事宜让我很不舒服这一点
It's... it's like, a...
这... 这就像是...
an itch in my brain I can't scratch.
大脑有点痒 我却挠不到
When I broke my arm I used
我手臂骨折的时候
to stick a coat hanger down there.
就那衣架插这儿挠痒
You ever try that? Maybe go in through the ear?
你试过吗? 插耳朵里挠挠?
You wouldn't make jokes if you could feel the way I feel.
如果你明白我的感受 就不会开这种玩笑
Well, I don't know how to do that.
我也没法明白你的感受
How about this?
这样如何?
I promise I won't pester you about the DVD.
我保证不会为影碟的事纠缠你
You can defecate in peace.
上厕所也不会骚扰你
That's a win for both of us.
这是双赢
But...
但是...
until this matter is resolved,
在这件事解决之前
I would like you
我要你
to wear this sweater.
穿着这毛衣
With nothing underneath it.
里面还不准穿其它衣服
That's stupid.
这太蠢了
Why?
为什么?
You say it's itchy and uncomfortable.
你说了这毛衣穿着扎人 不舒服
I say situations like this make me feel the same way.
在我看来 这件事给我的感受完全相同
I'm telling you, try the hanger.
我跟你说了 试试看用衣架挠
Put it on.
穿上
Let's share the experience.
我们来分享一下这感受
You got it.
好吧
If this sweater shuts you up,
如果穿上这件毛衣就能让你闭嘴的话
I'm gonna make a fortune
大家都会来买的
selling them to everyone we know.
那我就发财了
Now...
至于现在...
all I need to do
我只需要
is head down to the video store
到楼下的光盘店
and return the DVD.
把影碟还回去就行了
Oh, did I forget to tell you?
哦 我是不是忘记告诉你了?
That store went out of business years ago.
那家店好几年前就关门了
Really?
真的?
How those nipples feeling, chief?
你的咪咪感觉如何?
Penny, can we please get our drinks?
Penny 能把我俩的饮料给我们不?
Yeah, hang on, just give me sec.
好啊 稍等一下
At work today, I did an in vivo stereotaxic surgery.
今天上班的时候 我做了活体立体定位手术
Cool. At my lab,
高端啊 今天我在实验室里
I performed ten laser capture micro-dissections.
做了十次激光捕获微切割
I scraped gum off the bottom of that table.
我今天从那张桌子底下扣下来了一块口香糖
Only because my manager saw me put it there.
就因为经理看见是我粘在那的
Oh, my gosh.
天啊
That's the girl that broke Rajesh's heart.
她就是那个让Rajesh伤心欲绝的女孩
That's Lucy?
是Lucy?
I don't know why but I always pictured her as Indian.
我不知道为什么 但是我总把她想象成印度人
I think that reason's called racism.
貌似这就叫种族歧视吧
I'm gonna go talk to her.
我要去跟她聊聊
Why? What are you gonna say?
为什么? 你想说什么啊?
I'm not gonna say anything.
我不会乱说的
I just want to check her out
我就是想去见见她
because she hurt my friend.
因为她伤害了我朋友
My Indian friend.
我的印度朋友
Who's racist now?
现在是谁种族歧视?
You because you just called him
你啊 因为你刚把他叫做你的
your "Indian friend."
"印度朋友"
Yeah, well, you're short.
好吧 总之你长不高
We're never getting our drinks.
我们再也喝不上饮料了
No, but we knew that.
反正也不抱期望
Hey, can I start you off with something to drink?
嗨 想先喝点什么呢?
Oh, water would be great.
哦 水就行
Okay.
好的
Um, you're Lucy, right?
呃 你是Lucy?
I'm a friend of Raj Koothrappali's.
我是Raj Koothrappali的朋友
Actually Amy recognized you.
其实是Amy认出来的你
Wow.
哇
How's he doing?
他现在怎么样?
Oh, you know, he's good.
哦 你懂的啊 还好啦
Great.
那就好
Yeah, this is none of my business.
其实 这事跟我没什么关系
But why did you break up with him in an e-mail?
不过 你为什么要用发邮件的方式跟他分手?
Oh, I don't know.
我也不知道
I guess I thought it would be easier.
可能就是觉得这样比较容易吧
Yeah, I get that.
好吧 我懂了
I'll go get you your water.
我去给你拿杯水
When you say "easier,"
你说"容易"的意思是
you mean easier for you, right?
这对于你来说更容易 对吧?
Because it certainly didn't make it easier for him.
因为显然对他来说这根本不容易
Any chance I can get
我能不能
a different waitress?
换个服务员?
I... I'm sorry, this is rude of me.
对... 对不起 是我不好
I will go get that water.
我去给你拿水
See, see, see, see.
你看 你看 你看
Just now you expressed your feelings to my face.
就在刚才 你面对面地告诉我你的感受了
How come you could do that with me, but not Raj?
为什么你能这么面对我 却不能这么面对Raj?
I don't know your e-mail.
因为我不知道你的邮箱啊
You know what the worst part is?
你知道最糟糕的是什么吗?
You're sitting here, perfectly happy
你现在开开心心地坐在这里
and he's at home, a blubbering mess.
他却窝在家里哭成一团
Oh, I thought you said he was okay.
哦 你刚才不是说他挺好的嘛
Well, I also said I was getting you water,
是啊 我还说要给你拿水呢
but look at me still standing here.
我不还是站在这里么
You know, I may be a bad waitress,
知道吗 我可能不是个好服务员
but you are a bad person.
但你根本就是个坏人
Now, you want to hear the specials?
现在 要听听今天的特价菜是什么吗?
So, you can never take it off?
所以你永远不能脱下来?
No.
不能
Not even to sleep?
睡觉的时候也不行?
So, you're just an idiot?
你简直就是个白痴
It's called proving a point.
这是在摆明立场
Is the point you're an idiot?
那立场就是你是个白痴?
Gentlemen, please.
先生们 听我说
Leonard is trying to walk a mile in my metaphorical shoes.
Leonard正在努力感同身受呢(直译为穿我的鞋)
He can't walk in my actual shoes.
他穿不了我真实的鞋
He has the feet of a toddler.
他那脚只能穿童鞋呢
So, how are you gonna return the DVD
要是那家店已经停业了的话
if the store went out of business?
你打算怎么还光盘?
Monday morning I'll go downtown
周一早上我要去趟市中心
look up the owner's information.
找找店主的信息
And send him the DVD.
然后把光盘寄给他
Pay the late fee.
再把罚款交了
And prove to Sheldon
这样 我就可以向Sheldon证明
that you can have a problem and solve it...
不用那么抓狂...
without acting like a complete lunatic.
也可以发现并解决问题了
Ah!
哈!
And the man impersonating a bear would like everyone
扮狗熊的人还想让每个人都知道(指美国林务局的吉祥物Smokey熊)
to know that "Only you can prevent forest fires."
"只有你能防止森林火灾"呢
I don't get it.
什么意思
You didn't have Smokey the Bear in India?
你们印度没有Smokey熊吗?
No. Oh, is he anything like, uh, Mun-Mun the Mongoose?
没有 哦 他是不是和猫鼬萌萌差不多?
He taught us not to play with cobras.
萌萌告诉我们不要招惹眼镜蛇
You had to be taught not to play with cobras?
不要招惹眼镜蛇还用人教?
You had to be taught
还有人教你们
not to burn down the forest?
不能烧了森林呢 对吧?
Hey, if you guys were hungry, why didn't you order
嘿 你们要是饿了的话
something at the restaurant?
为什么在餐厅的时候不要点吃的?
We did, you never brought it.
我们要了 你一直没给我们啊
Oh, that's right.
哦 想起来了
Nachos and a turkey club.
是栗米脆饼和火鸡
Not even close.
差的也太远了吧
Well, I was too busy standing up
我是忙着给朋友出气
for my friend to worry about your...
才忘了你们的...
I want to say
我想想该说什么
salmon.
是三文鱼吧
You want to say sorry.
还是说对不起吧
So, how are you gonna tell Raj abut what you did?
你要怎么跟Raj说你干的好事?
What do you mean "how"? What's the big deal?
什么叫"怎么说"? 这有什么大不了的?
You told Lucy he was a pathetic mess.
你跟Lucy说Raj现在可怜兮兮 生活一团糟
Then you made her cry and leave.
后来你还把人家弄哭了 气走了
Okay, you guys are overreacting.
好啦 你们太小题大做了
Raj is gonna appreciate how I had his back.
我为Raj报了一箭之仇 他会感谢我的
What is wrong with you, Penny?!
你脑子被驴踢了吗 Penny?
You ruined any chance I had
我跟Lucy重修旧好的机会
of getting back with Lucy!
都让你给毁了!
Now she knows I'm a desperate mess
现在她实实在在知道我是个惨兮兮的可怜虫啦
instead of just being pretty sure!
以前她只不过是很肯定而已
It's Lucy.
是Lucy
She wants to meet for coffee.
她想约我喝咖啡
I love you, Penny!
爱死你啦 Penny!
Hey, what're you working on?
嘿 在忙什么呢?
I'm thinking about
我在想
how one could use the fact
高速旋转的镜子
that a rapidly rotating mirror
能让假光子变成成真的光子
turns virtual photons into real ones
那我们是否可以利用这种现象
as a method of observing dark energy.
来探索观察暗能量的方法呢
That's a pretty cool idea.
这想法很酷
Yeah. It's great you're here.
耶 你来得正好
I'd love to get an engineer's opinion.
我想听听工程师的看法
Sure.
没问题
This chair is squeaky.
这把椅子老是咯吱咯吱响
Now, do I fix it or get a new one?
能修好吗? 不行我再换一把
Well, Sheldon, it took me all morning,
啊哈 Sheldon 我浪费了一早上的时间
but I found the owner of the video store.
找到那家影碟店的老板了
And I am happy to report that he died peacefully in his sleep,
但是 听好了 他已经死翘翘了 喝醉后安详地睡死过去了
drunk at the bottom of a pool.
沉到了游泳池底部
Anyway, there is no one to return the DVD to,
总之就是 这张DVD还不回去了
so this issue is resolved.
所以 跟你的恩怨到此结束
Ah...
哈...
And I'd just like to point out that
我还想说
even though the sweater was uncomfortable,
虽然这件毛衣快把我扎死了
I didn't use it as an excuse
我也没有以此为借口
to antagonize everyone around me.
找身边任何人的茬儿
You know, you could reimburse
貌似你可以还给
the video store owner's next of kin.
影碟店老板的某个亲戚啊
Or it's resolved!
我说了到此结束!
Hey, that next of kin thing sounds pretty good.
嘿 Haward的主意听起来很不错哦
This is yours.
给你 不谢
Can I ask you guys a question?
问你俩一个问题
So, I'm seeing Lucy tomorrow night,
我明天晚上要见Lucy
and I've never hung out with someone who broke up with me.
我还从没跟已经跟我分手的人约会过
How do you do it?
该怎么做呢
You can't let her know you're hurting.
别让她知道你被她伤害了
You know, the key is confidence.
关键是自信
Why is the key always confidence?
为什么关键总是自信?
How come it's never love handles and flop sweat?
怎么从来都不是腰上的赘肉和紧张出来的汗呢?
If this girl hurt you so much,
这个女孩伤你那么深
are you sure you want to see her again?
你确定还想见她?
Well, if I may...
呃 容我插一句
he has so little self-respect
他几乎没啥自尊
and is so desperate
又极其渴望
for the smallest crumb of affection,
哪怕是一星半点的关爱
she could literally sleep with his own father
Lucy就算是跟他老爹滚床单
in his own bed and post the video to YouTube,
并且把视频传到YouTube上
and he'd still buy her flowers
这笨蛋还会给她买花
and ask her to be his bride.
向她求婚呢
He's right.
没错
But in my defense, if we could survive that,
但是 叫我说啊 是可忍
we could survive anything.
孰不可忍
Well, if you're sure you want to do this,
好吧 既然你确定你想见她
it's only coffee...
那就只是喝喝咖啡
just relax and see what happens.
心态放轻松 顺其自然吧
Well, can I say she looks nice?
那 我能夸她漂亮不?
Sure.
当然
Can I tell her I miss her?
我能告诉她我想她了吗？
Maybe, if she asks.
看情况 要是她问的话
Oh, can I show her an oil painting I made
哦 我能让她看看我画的一幅油画吗?
of us surrounded by our children and grandchildren?
上面画着我俩儿孙绕膝
I'd save that for the second date.
还是下次约会再看吧
Good, good.
好主意 好主意
'Cause no matter how hard I try,
我反复试了很多次
I cannot get the twins to look alike.
还是没能把那对双胞胎画得一样
What are you doing?
你在干嘛？
Oh, I'm just trying to find the stupid next of kin
噢 我要找到那个傻叉老板的
to this stupid video store owner
傻叉亲戚
so I can return the DVD
这样我就可以归还那张影碟
and see the look on Sheldon's stupid face
看到Sheldon脸上的傻叉表情了
when he sees that I didn't let this get to me.
我要让他知道 这点儿事哪能难倒我
Sheldon's not here.
Sheldon又不在这儿
Why don't you take the sweater off?
为啥不把毛衣脱了呢?
Th-Th-There's a principle at stake!
这-这-这是原则问题!
- Which is?  - Oh, I don't know.
- 什么原则?  - 噢 不知道
Who cares? Look at me!
很重要吗? 看看我!
Oh, my God!
噢 老天爷!
Is that sweater made of bees?
那是件毛衣 还是个蜂窝啊
Come on, take it off. I won't tell.
快点 脱下来 我不会出卖你的
No, no, honey, if I take it off, Sheldon wins.
不 不行 亲爱的 要是我脱了 Sheldon就赢了
Sweetie...
亲
every night you don't kill him in his sleep,
每天晚上你没在他熟睡的时候杀了他
he wins.
就已经是他赢了
Nah, i-it's... it's almost done.
哎呀 就-就快熬到头了
I just, I have to find...
我 我只用找到
the next of kin, and send 'em the DVD
他的亲戚 把影碟还回去
and then just wait for someone with my complexion to die
接下来就皱着个苦瓜脸等某人来
so I can get a skin graft.
然后我就去做个制皮手术
Smile.
笑
What-what is that?
干啥-什么呀?
What is that for?
拍我干啥?
So you can send it to Princeton
发给普利斯顿大学
and get your money back.
把你交的学费要回来（这么笨 学都白上了）
I must say, Sheldon,
不得不说 Sheldon
you're handling this DVD business
DVD这件事你处理得相当老练
with an impressive amount of maturity.
叫人佩服呀
I don't know why that surprises you.
真奇怪 这你都会觉得惊喜
I'm a grown man.
我已经是个成年人了
As should be evident by this sport coat
从我这身行头不也能看出来嘛
and very real flower in my lapel.
短外套 翻领上别一朵高仿花朵
Is there some kind of new coping mechanism you're employing?
你正在使用什么新的问题应对机制吗?
The more interesting question you should be asking is:
你更应该问
"What does this flower smell like?"
"这朵花什么味道?"
I'm gonna go with sad.
我猜是悲伤的味道
So what's the story
说说是怎么回事
with you and this DVD?
你和这DVD到底怎么了?
There's nothing to tell.
没什么
Maybe I purchased a book entitled,
我买了一本书
Don't Sweat the Small Stuff
题目叫"不要为小事苦恼"
and I followed its wise suggestions,
它里面的建议挺不错的
one of which was:
其中有一条:
stop and smell the flowers.
停下来闻闻花香
Seriously?
真的吗?
Please.
求你了
Ha-ha!
哈哈!
Oh.
哦
- Hi.  - Hello.
- 嗨  - 你好
Oh, it's so good to see you.
见到你真高兴
You, too.
我也是
Please, sit.
请坐吧
I, uh, I got you a cappuccino.
我给你点了一杯卡布奇诺
I remembered it was your favorite.
我记得这是你的最爱
Oh. I also got crumb cake,
哦 我还点了面包屑
but I remembered it was my favorite and I ate it.
但后来想起来这是我的最爱 所以我就把它吃了
Anyway, uh, how are you?
好吧 你怎么样?
I'm pretty good.
还不错
Listen, I just wanted to apologize
真是很抱歉
for breaking up with you in an e-mail.
用电子邮件跟你分手
Well, and I ate all the crumb cake.
我把面包屑全吃掉了
We both made mistakes.
我们都有做的不好的地方嘛
Okay.
好吧
I'm so happy you asked me here,
你约我出来太让我高兴了
and I hope we can hang out again sometime.
希望以后我们也能常一起出来玩
You know, as friends,
就像朋友那样
lovemaking partners, whatever.
或是炮友神马的
Oh, uh...
哦...
I'm kind of seeing someone.
我已经有对象了
I think I know the answer to this,
我知道这显而易见
but just to be clear, it's not me, right?
不过还是想确认一下 你说的不是我 是吧?
This is all your fault!
这都怪你!
I should've listened to Mun-Mun
我应该听萌萌的话
because I've been playing with a cobra
因为我竟然和眼镜蛇一起玩
and her name is Penny!
她叫Penny!
Why are you so cruel?
你怎么那么残忍?
Do you enjoy my pain?
看到我心碎你很开心吗?
There's a girl at the Cheesecake Factory I can set you up with.
起司蛋糕店有个女孩 我可以介绍给你认识
I love you, Penny!
爱死你了 Penny!
How is it I can conceptualize a methodology
为什么我能解释清楚
of examining dark matter in the universe
检测宇宙黑暗物质的方法论
but can't figure out how to fix a novelty squirt flower?
却搞不明白怎么修好一朵喷水花?
I think the real question is,
其实问题在于
why do you waste your time with cheap, childish pranks?
你为什么要浪费时间修理这个小孩子的玩意儿?
There's probably a deep reason.
这是一个很深奥的问题
Which I'd be happy to discuss with you
我想一边品尝花生碎
over some peanut brittle in a can.
一边与你探讨
Okay, Sheldon, I am out of options!
好吧 Sheldon 我受够了!
Video store owner, Nursis Manookian,
音像店老板Nursis Manookian
has no next of kin!
根本没有亲属!
Well, you seem hot under the collar...
你看起来有点热...
or is that the sweater?
是因为毛衣吗?
Oh, oh, no, no.
哦 不 不
It... It's because I spent all afternoon
是因为整个下午
at the Armenian church where his funeral mass was held.
都在亚美尼亚教堂参加他的葬礼
According to Father Solakian,
听Solakian神父说
no one attended.
没有别人会去
Luckily, my trip wasn't a complete waste.
还好我没有白走一趟
I lit a candle and prayed for your death.
我点了根蜡烛 祈祷上帝快点把你带走
But I'm not Armenian, so it probably won't work!
但我不是亚美尼亚人 所以应该不灵验!
This is over, right?
这事结了 是吧?
Oh, not necessarily.
还不一定
I suggest
我建议
you look for long-lost relatives
你去亚米尼亚或是黎巴嫩
either in Armenia or Lebanon.
寻一下亲
Listen to me, Sheldon.
听着 Sheldon
I am not going to Lebanon
我不会去黎巴嫩
to return Super Mario Bros. the movie!
只为还"超级玛丽兄弟"这部电影!
You know, it might be fun.
或许很有意思呢
You love hummus.
你喜欢鹰嘴豆泥
Why isn't this bothering you?
为什么你不烦恼?
It... Isn't your brain getting itchy?
难道你心里就不会不安吗?
This is on your card.
这是用你的卡租的
This could be ruining your credit score!
这会给你带来不良信用记录的!
Why isn't this making you crazy?
你怎么能忍呢?
Leonard...
Leonard 听着...
I have something to tell you,
我要跟你说件事
but I want you to promise not to flip out.
但你要答应我 别发疯
What?
什么事?
Seven years ago,
七年前
I found out the DVD was late
我发现这个DVD租期到了
and I paid for it.
于是就把它买了下来
What?
再说一遍?
I was going to mention it at the time,
我本来想告诉你的
but then I thought, some day,
但后来又想 有一天
this might be a teachable moment.
可能这个能给某人一点教训
Hah...
啊...
I... you...
我... 你...
How can...
怎么...
What?!
怎么?!
Sheldon...
哦 Sheldon...
that was diabolical.
这么做太坏了
I know.
我知道
And it wasn't easy.
太艰辛了
Do you have any idea what it's like
苦等了这么多年
to wait for years and never know
只想看谁能笑到最后
who would finally get satisfaction?
你知道这有多难熬吗?
Wow.
哇
You're even prettier than Penny said.
你比Penny说的还漂亮
I can't believe
难以置信
a girl like you doesn't have a boyfriend.
你这样的女孩竟然没有男朋友
Well, I don't.
确实没有
I don't believe you, you're lying to me!
我才不信 你这个骗子!
What?
你说什么?
Oh, it's okay.
哦 没什么
I have no morals and I'm desperately lonely.
我已经寂寞得没有节操了
I'll be the other man
如果你喜欢踏两只船
if you want a little something-something on the side.
我也觉得无所谓啊
What is wrong with you?!
你脑袋被驴踢了吧?!
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==-- 仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==-- 仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见 时间轴：pisces夜 翻译：失眠影 学渣酥 Wholessness 初见 校对：uu要A
协调：初见 时间轴：pisces夜 翻译：失眠影 学渣酥 Wholessness 初见 校对：uu要A